$FSOC_MOD_NAME	Free Sprint Out of Combat
$FSOC_ABOUT	Sprinting costs no Action Points while you are out of combat, and Action Points keep regenerating as if you were standing still.
$FSOC_SEC_MAIN	Settings
$FSOC_IN_COMBAT	Free sprint in combat too
$FSOC_IN_COMBAT_HELP	When on, sprinting costs no AP in combat as well.
$FSOC_SEC_POWER_ARMOR	Power armor
$FSOC_PA_AP	Free sprint in power armor
$FSOC_PA_AP_HELP	When on, sprinting in power armor costs no AP either. When off, sprinting in power armor costs AP as usual.
$FSOC_PA_CORE	Economical fusion core drain
$FSOC_PA_CORE_HELP	When on, sprinting in power armor drains the fusion core as if you covered the same distance at a normal run. When off, the core drains as usual.
